<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <description>Hearsay and conjecture from a current &lt;a href=&quot;http://turing.io&quot;&gt;Turing School&lt;/a&gt; student.
</description>
    <link>http://shim.city/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://shim.city/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2015 19:40:13 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2015 19:40:13 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.4.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to Jekyll!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code&gt;jekyll serve --watch&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention &lt;code&gt;YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext&lt;/code&gt; and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&amp;#39;Tom&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints &amp;#39;Hi, Tom&amp;#39; to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll-help&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s dedicated Help repository&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2015 15:49:02 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://shim.city/jekyll/update/2015/07/03/welcome-to-jekyll.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://shim.city/jekyll/update/2015/07/03/welcome-to-jekyll.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Bacon Ipsum!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Bacon ipsum dolor amet rump porchetta tenderloin swine landjaeger salami pork belly kielbasa beef ribs flank ribeye. Pancetta turkey boudin pastrami leberkas, prosciutto turducken ribeye bacon pig shank jerky ball tip rump. Fatback boudin turkey jowl, cupim landjaeger ball tip. Short loin pancetta fatback kielbasa.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Landjaeger jowl bacon, venison turducken pig meatloaf drumstick pork tri-tip short ribs filet mignon. Drumstick sausage andouille turducken ham pork, shoulder alcatra biltong boudin filet mignon. Shankle tenderloin doner flank tail. Cow ham short loin turkey shankle kielbasa short ribs. Tongue ground round tenderloin, kielbasa ham hock swine sausage corned beef porchetta short loin alcatra boudin shoulder venison capicola. Sirloin salami corned beef, ground round filet mignon brisket meatball hamburger rump pork loin. Porchetta meatloaf landjaeger, cupim jowl doner ham filet mignon pastrami fatback tri-tip chuck short loin pork spare ribs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bacon prosciutto ham hock cupim chicken jerky biltong swine pork loin pastrami strip steak shank. Sausage meatloaf cupim leberkas tri-tip andouille salami drumstick. Alcatra short loin pork, chicken ball tip meatball beef ribs frankfurter turducken andouille jerky jowl. Alcatra cupim shankle andouille picanha pork belly, salami capicola pancetta cow venison sausage tri-tip meatloaf porchetta. Capicola short loin hamburger venison, bacon brisket alcatra ribeye picanha tenderloin salami ball tip shank spare ribs pork chop. Landjaeger picanha drumstick bresaola doner, tri-tip pig short loin spare ribs jowl chuck hamburger t-bone andouille tail.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jul 2015 15:49:02 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://shim.city/test/2015/07/02/bacon-ipsum.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://shim.city/test/2015/07/02/bacon-ipsum.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>test</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
